<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Casual on Yarsa Games</title>
    <link>http://192.168.1.18/categories/casual/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Casual on Yarsa Games</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://192.168.1.18/categories/casual/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Direction</title>
      <link>http://192.168.1.18/post/2-direction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://192.168.1.18/post/2-direction/</guid>
      <description>2 Direction is an exciting casual game for everyday gaming. You have to drive a marble along a zigzag path and collect as many diamonds as you can.
Tap for left and tap for right. Stay on the lane, do not fall and collect the Diamonds. Challenge yourself to your own high score; if you are a challenge lover you can browse the leaderboard and beat everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balls Again</title>
      <link>http://192.168.1.18/post/balls-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://192.168.1.18/post/balls-again/</guid>
      <description>Awesome to play. Great time killer Awesome to play. Great time killer Awesome to play. Great time killer Awesome to play. Great time killer Awesome to play. Great time killer Awesome to play. Great time killer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heart Rush</title>
      <link>http://192.168.1.18/post/heart-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://192.168.1.18/post/heart-rush/</guid>
      <description>Heart rush is a simple game. Drag your heart around, collect other hearts and grow bigger. Avoid any broken hearts, or you’ll lose. Easily navigate with invisible joystick like controls.
Heart rush was made on Valentines week of 2018.
With :cupid: from Yarsa Games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jumper</title>
      <link>http://192.168.1.18/post/jumper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://192.168.1.18/post/jumper/</guid>
      <description>Tap to jump and collect diamonds. Jump Until you beat the highest number of among all players. There is only 1 way to survive – jump until your last breath. Do not touch the spikes and collect the points. Enjoy the game.
This game is a part of one day game developing challenge. This game took less than 24 hours to build from scratch and is published within that time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>