<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Yarsa Games</title>
    <link>http://192.168.1.18/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Yarsa Games</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://192.168.1.18/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Callbreak, Kitty, Solitaire &amp; Jutpatti</title>
      <link>http://192.168.1.18/post/all-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://192.168.1.18/post/all-cards/</guid>
      <description>Play multiple popular card games in single application. It consist of 4 popular games currently. 1. Callbreak 2. Kitty 3. Solitaire 4. Jutpatti
More games will be added shortly. Thank you for trying the game. Pleas feel free to submit any feedback. We’re constantly adding new levels and features to the game. Your feedback will make the game even better for everyone.
All the best!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Driving School Nepal Drive Car, Bus &amp; Motorcycle</title>
      <link>http://192.168.1.18/post/nepal-driving-trial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://192.168.1.18/post/nepal-driving-trial/</guid>
      <description>Driving School Nepal is the first driver’s license test game for Nepal, dedicated to car, bus, motorcycle and scooter license. If you are looking forward to Nepalese driving license test, and you&amp;rsquo;ve enrolled in an driving academy to practice driving, we recommend this game for you. You can prepare for road signs test as well as driving test with the help of this driving simulator game. For a start, the game includes four different categories – 🏍Motorcycle riding – 🛴Scooter riding – 🚘Car driving test – 🚌Bus driving test</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jumper</title>
      <link>http://192.168.1.18/post/jumper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://192.168.1.18/post/jumper/</guid>
      <description>Tap to jump and collect diamonds. Jump Until you beat the highest number of among all players. There is only 1 way to survive – jump until your last breath. Do not touch the spikes and collect the points. Enjoy the game.
This game is a part of one day game developing challenge. This game took less than 24 hours to build from scratch and is published within that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dunk</title>
      <link>http://192.168.1.18/post/dunk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://192.168.1.18/post/dunk/</guid>
      <description>One touch easy basketball dunk game. Super cool graphics. Many balls to choose and unlock. Global leader board. Achievements to unlock. Dunk the ball to get higher score. This game have almost no ads. Only rewarded ad are included.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Missile-Escape</title>
      <link>http://192.168.1.18/post/missile-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://192.168.1.18/post/missile-escape/</guid>
      <description>Dodge your way through the missiles and survive along the journey with missile escape. Challenge yourself to fight for the best score and time. Destroy missiles and earn coins to unlock all new 10 planes for more adventure and thrilling experience. Change your plane direction using joystick or you can choose hover option to move your finger all over screen to move plane. Share your experience over social networks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balls Again</title>
      <link>http://192.168.1.18/post/balls-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://192.168.1.18/post/balls-again/</guid>
      <description>Awesome to play. Great time killer Awesome to play. Great time killer Awesome to play. Great time killer Awesome to play. Great time killer Awesome to play. Great time killer Awesome to play. Great time killer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curveline</title>
      <link>http://192.168.1.18/post/curveline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://192.168.1.18/post/curveline/</guid>
      <description>Curveline is simple and addictive type of game. Just tap to move the line right or left and move forward dodging the obstacles and score the points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heart Rush</title>
      <link>http://192.168.1.18/post/heart-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://192.168.1.18/post/heart-rush/</guid>
      <description>Heart rush is a simple game. Drag your heart around, collect other hearts and grow bigger. Avoid any broken hearts, or you’ll lose. Easily navigate with invisible joystick like controls.
Heart rush was made on Valentines week of 2018.
With :cupid: from Yarsa Games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ski Ball</title>
      <link>http://192.168.1.18/post/ski-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://192.168.1.18/post/ski-ball/</guid>
      <description>Ski Ball is an awesome fun game with simple controls. Ski down the mountain, do not hit the trees but don’t forget to collect the points from the trees. Enjoy skiing in the chilled snow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dodge Cube</title>
      <link>http://192.168.1.18/post/dodge-cube/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://192.168.1.18/post/dodge-cube/</guid>
      <description>Dodge cube is an addictive game with simple gameplay. Tilt your phone or tap left and right to dodge falling cubes and stay alive as much as you can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balls Rush Space</title>
      <link>http://192.168.1.18/post/ballsrush-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://192.168.1.18/post/ballsrush-space/</guid>
      <description>Balls Rush is an adventure game, that features a planet ball rushing ahead in space, while being followed by a bunch of enemy balls. Enemy balls rush towards you, and will destroy you.
To survive the balls rush, you have to tackle the obstacles swiftly so that the enemy balls will get struck and destroyed. As times goes, the rush intensifies. Time starts running faster, the balls will start moving towards you faster and faster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basketball Free Throw</title>
      <link>http://192.168.1.18/post/basketball-throw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://192.168.1.18/post/basketball-throw/</guid>
      <description>Basketball Throw is an endless game where you try to score as many scores as possible. Collect stars along the way, choose from various balls with different physics and you’ll be playing the game for hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Direction</title>
      <link>http://192.168.1.18/post/2-direction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://192.168.1.18/post/2-direction/</guid>
      <description>2 Direction is an exciting casual game for everyday gaming. You have to drive a marble along a zigzag path and collect as many diamonds as you can.
Tap for left and tap for right. Stay on the lane, do not fall and collect the Diamonds. Challenge yourself to your own high score; if you are a challenge lover you can browse the leaderboard and beat everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2D Fall</title>
      <link>http://192.168.1.18/post/2d-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://192.168.1.18/post/2d-fall/</guid>
      <description>2D Fall can be your best time killer game ever. It’s a physics based rock falling game, with easy controls and challenging gameplay. You can also switch between different balls with multiple characteristics. Collect coins and get your balls unlocked and enjoy game.
How to play Just tap right or left part of screen to control the rock fall from on plank to other.
Let’s see how much you can fall.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>